A letter from October 5, 2022. Dear future me,
wherever you are and whatever you are doing, stop right now and just breathe.
Take a moment to take it all in and allow yourself a moment just for
you. Allow yourself a moment of rest, a moment
of quiet, a moment to do something just for you. You have
been working so hard these past few months, and it's okay to slow down or
even stop altogether and just rest. You deserve it.
It you deserve time to reset and take care of you. Whatever time
you carve out for yourself is not selfish. It is a must. So you can
be a better mom, a better caregiver, a better friend, a better confidant,
a better version of you. I hope you have an amazing day. And please
know that I am proud of all of your efforts. All of the long hours
and sacrifices to reach your goals and improve your life have all been
worth it. Just don't forget to enjoy the present moment while you're working so
hard to achieve your dream.